well back Skokie's photoshoot
exclamation points
I don't think I should get on Wi-Fi
don't you think
well was pretty good my ulti is better
no it's not it's not it's not divided
are you guys happy with the Wi-Fi Scopus
what's up this is my photo shoot look I
might hand you I'm ahead um I hand you
over to Vivian
yo yeah comment nowhere ha has always
been here yeah we're doing a photoshoot
folks doing a photoshoot okay it could
be mine no purple night so I'm proud of
my purple fear uh y'all guys 2:49
hoodies I'm gonna be real I tried this
hoodie on shocked at how cool it is and
I I literally hadn't tried one on since
making them all the hoodies yeah exactly
I did yeah Philippine it's professional
developments right yes
but guys we got to be profitable in q1
we're gonna be profit I was hoping for
an Zevon Shay photo shoot Oh y'all I
didn't buy the cheap on check guys all
right remember how I used to talk about
little people all the time but what
people lo people oh yes have a lot to me
the peeps dead honestly who keeps dead
and he was kind of 2017 you know who's
2018 you guys no no we're shilling for
Logan Paul bro ever since I found Logan
ball my life has changed I've had so
much 22 he lives in LA in a mansion
there's been so much positivity in my
life Logan I hope you're hearing this
that's right don't by the way like if he
wants to make that Yeti self-driving I
don't do it I would actually think you
two assuming are profitable in q1 yeah
no we got we had some amazing the y'all
should know so the yetis not a real car
the Yeti is just what he named his big
bend's you know you gotta like step all
the way up into that thing yeah so you
guys get there we're doing a photo shoot
right now
are we loyal willow we're like always
the boy so much everybody but it go to
comedy I slash shop that links not live
yet for now yeah really soon understand
you were live kamidana okay when Logan
Paul does it like the words appear on
the screen it's Christy and it's videos
we should do that we gotta start do it
no yeah think I'm gonna do that real one
yeah that'd be good let's hold up with
these paper then be just as good but
know what we're doing we're doing a
photo shoot today the reason reason I
don't know I don't know obviously Reggie
interviewer watch the interview I got
600,000 views on YouTube which is a lot
less than bug and fall but you know one
day one day LP you know one day you guys
got me yes me honestly
PewDiePie might actually talk about us
yeah cutie pie I'm a big beauty we're
big beautiful fast we I didn't know
recently no but honestly guys lacks for
the 2019 we're moving to a mansion in LA
yeah
after comas this is gonna be our success
yeah this is it this is really this is
the year 18:18 emerges the merchants
flying off the shelf over should really
watch it is we have an entire mushroom
would you have a merger oh that you but
we do shipping us know we can show on
the Mercer we don't know the numbers
yeah but let's just say millions of
dollars yes the sauce all will say I'm
also in good care yourself or the scope
these are 3 p.m. Pacific time tomorrow
we're gonna do a CES presentation we're
not at CES we don't go it's too full of
fake chills we like real shifts you know
what I mean Logan Paul like his friends
dog dies and he's like
sad but you can check out the new
maverick merchandise and like oh my god
bless shop yeah when duty on ship in
once the key OVR say they just made it
so pragmatics okay like what you guys
here for don't you just want to see us
be the photoshoot yeah everybody it's a
beautiful day in sunny San fits aboard
yeah they're interested in the
photoshoot and join explain with that
does do I show my motorcycle oh man
rules this is George's motorcycle it's
dead
yeah yeah and I need more - a foldable
pizza board winning yeah p.m. tonight
Wow 50m Pacific time tomorrow tomorrow
we're gonna be announcing a new product
you read out your new variant of a
product there oh yeah very exciting
stuff this guy's great
he's gay we're gonna be on periscope for
you guys periscope for you 3 3 p.m. it's
gonna be like CES style but what our
products I don't know yes do you guys
know what's really happening in C at CES
it seems the usual yeah I want to see
alright let's go we'll get the group all
right who wants to be in the photo shoot
anyone before we need people Eddie yeah
yeah yeah we for sure sure yeah we are
sweatshirt miss Richards so
so we're ordering new ones so for for
the people who ordered sweatshirts we're
ordering new ones don't worry about it
yet so we have hats for the people wait
a second now I'm just I'm just having
skill fees in this there's nothing
happening scope is hanging yes
sixty-three don't miss this face seeing
him 20 minutes every day when we gonna
what are they gonna call me now you've
got for me so says Eddie Oh vanilla
gorilla obviously hit vanilla hey any
friend yeah I don't nobody spend
whatever trips I any Tosh noises it on
Hamra yeah I guess we're out oh this was
a great photo shoot to show you guys
look at this
we're printing shit but more importantly
how cool is that right yeah but it's for
photoshoot what are you wanting to be
word on the street is that the media
thinks that it's only George who works
for so they're like we should show that
your other employees so we're showing
you
Hey Oh Andy you want to say hi to the
Scopus yeah we're doing a photo shoot
yeah
you got some merch yeah merch sorrows
ghosts great good good we're still doing
this mother bleep 68 views maybe they
should be ended with this whole double
homeless coppice can't really see them
though that's kind of sad oh I'll just
still show it like you know I know
you're right but then they people know
how much we love our school they've been
here on this journey with us skull peas
is it gonna be Scopus forever like we
need like low gang or Jake Pollard's you
know comic thing right she's pretty
squad three squads out driving yeah um
grab some merch come on down research
that oh yeah grab no just grab some
sweat you've got we got whatever I got a
roadie oh oh yeah there's more of those
dents no they're not bad they're just
not for sale car awareness tour with us
you can't get one of those yeah well you
guys there's actually a real shortage of
what he's told this go babe yeah we're
getting more likes you would not believe
how much hoodies sell yeah you really
wouldn't believe it yeah we're gonna be
profitable off hoodies alone commit to a
hoodie company no I will be like supreme
if people is to prove Nate wait Oh
we got all kinds of merch dope is know
about all the for sale yeah it will be a
bit alive we need more shirts is that
we're saying merch wise up we are going
to do a t-shirt for you guys
how much scope is how much should we
charge for the t-shirt how much what are
you thinking
how much did Kanye charge for his will
be cheaper than Kanye I promise
50% off guy money people sex is funny
what about it free shit money a lot of
them are sleeping what a free shipping I
told you 20 man we're really gonna price
our shirts of 20 30 35 I think I think I
think we might be able to do $20 only
you know I you know what it's gonna be
25 but we're gonna put exclusive coupons
right here on our periscope you'll be
able to access it directly from
[Music]
how can you not look at George yeah
all right I mean to feel like that oh I
gotta get the car okay George sit up a
little bit
no I'm telling these guys though they
won't believe some of us if we have plan
for 2018 is back good
I spoke with that I spoke the journalist
this morning about you know why do you
always keep saying Tesla's ahead we
think the hustle is behind right did a
birch article last year at the end last
year and we told the reporter that we
could 50 people in the back of like this
tiny garage yeah and I think we'll wait
average projection we lie to reporters
sometimes they're cool reporters when
it's like how much is this costing me
per hour guys oh okay we have realized
you know like we're not even kidding
wait in there we're here
[Music]